{
  "quizInfo": {
    "Subject": "Mobile Systems and Technologies",
    "Term": "Midterms",
    "Title": "04 Handout 1 - User Interface",
    "LastModified": "11 March 2025",
    "Authors": [
      "Alexander Oro"
    ],
    "References": [
      "04 Handout 1"
    ]
  },
  "quizData": [
    {
      "question": "What defines the structure for an app's user interface?",
      "answer": "layout",
      "choices": [
        "View",
        "ViewGroup",
        "notification",
        "layout"
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which invisible container defines the layout structure for View and other objects?",
      "answer": "ViewGroup",
      "choices": [
        "View",
        "layout",
        "Frame Layout",
        "ViewGroup"
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "What draws something the user can see and interact with?",
      "answer": "View",
      "choices": [
        "ViewGroup",
        "Constraint Layout",
        "Web View",
        "View"
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which method separates the presentation of the app from the code that controls its behavior?",
      "answer": "Declare UI elements in XML",
      "choices": [
        "Instantiate layout elements at runtime",
        "Constraint Layout",
        "Linear Layout",
        "Declare UI elements in XML"
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which method allows View and ViewGroup objects to be created and manipulated programmatically?",
      "answer": "Instantiate layout elements at runtime",
      "choices": [
        "Declare UI elements in XML",
        "Frame Layout",
        "Table Layout",
        "Instantiate layout elements at runtime"
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "What provides an interface to global information about an application environment?",
      "answer": "Context",
      "choices": [
        "ViewGroup",
        "layout",
        "notification",
        "Context"
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which property sets the size of a view to the dimensions required by its content?",
      "answer": "wrap_content",
      "choices": [
        "match_parent",
        "width and height",
        "ViewGroup",
        "wrap_content"
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which property sets a view to be as big as its parent view allows?",
      "answer": "match_parent",
      "choices": [
        "wrap_content",
        "width and height",
        "Constraint Layout",
        "match_parent"
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which layout creates large and complex layouts with a flat view hierarchy?",
      "answer": "Constraint Layout",
      "choices": [
        "Linear Layout",
        "Relative Layout",
        "Grid Layout",
        "Constraint Layout"
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which layout organizes its child view elements into a single horizontal or vertical row?",
      "answer": "Linear Layout",
      "choices": [
        "Relative Layout",
        "Constraint Layout",
        "Frame Layout",
        "Linear Layout"
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which layout specifies the location of child objects relative to each other or the parent?",
      "answer": "Relative Layout",
      "choices": [
        "Linear Layout",
        "Grid Layout",
        "Table Layout",
        "Relative Layout"
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which layout is used for displaying web pages?",
      "answer": "Web View",
      "choices": [
        "Constraint Layout",
        "Relative Layout",
        "Grid Layout",
        "Web View"
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which layout is designed to block out an area on the screen to display a single item?",
      "answer": "Frame Layout",
      "choices": [
        "Table Layout",
        "Grid Layout",
        "Linear Layout",
        "Frame Layout"
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which layout arranges its child objects into rows and columns?",
      "answer": "Table Layout",
      "choices": [
        "Grid Layout",
        "Relative Layout",
        "Frame Layout",
        "Table Layout"
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which layout arranges its child objects in a rectangular grid that can be scrolled?",
      "answer": "Grid Layout",
      "choices": [
        "Table Layout",
        "Relative Layout",
        "Constraint Layout",
        "Grid Layout"
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a message that Android displays outside the appâ€™s UI for reminders or alerts?",
      "answer": "notification",
      "choices": [
        "dialog",
        "toast",
        "snackbar",
        "notification"
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which UI component allows viewing more details and taking actions with a notification?",
      "answer": "notification drawer",
      "choices": [
        "app bar",
        "dialog",
        "menu",
        "notification drawer"
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which UI component provides a visual structure and interactive elements for user navigation?",
      "answer": "app bar",
      "choices": [
        "dialog",
        "toast",
        "Frame Layout",
        "app bar"
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which part of the UI provides important actions like search and navigation?",
      "answer": "action bar",
      "choices": [
        "notification drawer",
        "menu",
        "toast",
        "action bar"
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which UI component provides simple feedback about an operation in a small popup?",
      "answer": "toast",
      "choices": [
        "snackbar",
        "dialog",
        "notification",
        "toast"
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which UI component provides a quick pop-up message to the user?",
      "answer": "snackbar",
      "choices": [
        "toast",
        "dialog",
        "notification",
        "snackbar"
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which UI component is a small window that prompts the user for a decision or input?",
      "answer": "dialog",
      "choices": [
        "toast",
        "snackbar",
        "menu",
        "dialog"
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which UI component presents user actions and other options in an app's activities?",
      "answer": "menu",
      "choices": [
        "dialog",
        "toast",
        "notification",
        "menu"
      ],
      "reference": "04 Handout 1",
      "term": "Midterms"
    }
  ]
}